K. Durga Bhavani

Contact: 8885150226

Email: dura.bhavani85@gmail.com

Objective

To be able to work and grow personally and professionally with the organization where I could use my skills, my endeavor and dedication in the work. I have 3 years of experience in analysis which can be used in my upcoming roles to transition from Trust and safety to a role in the data science field and also I have completed my masters in data sciences which is an added value.

Education

November 2021-2023

JNTUH, School of Information Technology, Hyderabad - M. TECH (Data Sciences)

Masters of Technology in Data science

Keshav Memorial Institute of Technology, Hyderabad - CSE

Bachelors of Technology in Computer science Engineering

Technical Skills

- Structured Query Language (SQL)
- Spreadsheets Excel, Sheets
- Data visualization tools Power BI
- Python programming

Project

Speech based Emotion Recognition using Convolutional Neural Network- MTECH

The basic idea behind this project is to build and train/test a suited machine learning as well as deep learning algorithm that could recognize and detect human emotions from speech.

Achievements

- Attended Deloitte workshop on Case Study of Cyber Security.
- Qualified the B2 Business Vantage Exam of Cambridge Business English Certificate (BEC)
- Conducted "Women in IT" session held in KMIT

Experience

Webhelp, Hyderabad - Quality Analyst

Tenure: May 2020 - September 2022

- Calibrated evaluations, produce alignment measure and insight
- Communicated direct feedback to evaluators to support improvement in alignment, agree SMART action plans, understand progress to plan and measure improvements
- Presented actionable insight, recommendations and local quality calibration plan
- Conducted site calibration to ensure consistency across the business
- Supported calibration accreditation initiative
- Collaborated with academy accreditation
- Completed complaint investigation and transcript requests
- Captured continuous improvement opportunities and close loop through effective coaching

Sitel, Hyderabad - Technical Support Analyst L1

Tenure: August 2019 - May 2020

- Troubleshooted and resolved basic issues utilizing company systems, utilities and support processes with assistance and direct oversight from team members
- Provided regular and frequent communication to customer with oversight; ensure customer is fully advised as to the progress or delay to the resolution of their issue
- Maintained ownership of and accountability for customer requests with oversight; maintain ownership of request and follow through consistently with resolution
- Monitored and picked up support cases from customers requesting assistance via internal company system with oversight
- Responded to inbound calls for products to support process or production down needs; create case and route to proper queue accordingly
- Researched and submitted software defect cases to internal team for review
- Collaborated with team for internal documentation to fully reflect all activity related to resolution of support request